Going back to what Rato said, frame layout, linear layout, and relative layout
are three of the most common layouts you will use in building out your UI.
These all descend from the view group class, designed to contain and
give order to child views. They each have their strengths and
you should always try to use this simplest layout that will get the job done.
Frame Layout is great for simple layouts when you only have one child to view,
like a list view that fills the entire content area. Linear layout is
perfect for stacking the views vertically or horizontally, one after another,
it is also the only way to break up the display proportionately. Relative layout
is powerful but a bit more complicated compared to the others. Throw a bunch of
views inside a relative layout, and then you can configure each views
position relative to parent, the relative layout, or to sibling views, tons of
possibilities. We'll explore these layouts in greater detail when we build more
complex screens. For now, let's get back to building our forecast list.